Sean Chaucer Levine

(908-285-5179) sean@ghostmouth.com Minneapolis, MN

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer, Educator, and Audio Engineer with direct and clear communication skills. Excels at debugging, team oriented web app projects, react, and design. Obsessed with troubleshooting, digesting new information, and creating iconic content. Knowledgeable and experienced at implementing a variety of different database languages, and a proficient performer and educator of over twelve musical instruments.

Portfolio: http://www.seanchaucerlevine.com Github: https://github.com/Ghostmouth

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-levine-a803a239/

Projects

Task Manager | https://github.com/hallek7/Titanic-float-none | https://guarded-sea-37827.herokuapp.com/
Server Routes & Front End

Integrates a SQL database with a task management database to store user information, project information, tasks, and deadlines. Utilizes mySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Sequelize, HTML5, CSS, node.JS, and Express.

News Scraper | https://github.com/Ghostmouth/newsscraper | https://mongoosehwassignment.herokuapp.com/ Full Stack Development

Scrapes news articles from NPR, with functionality to save and store articles, and comments to a mongo database. Utilizes mongoDB, mongoose, JavaScript, handlebars, HTML, CSS, and node.JS.

Band Website | https://github.com/Ghostmouth/ghostmouthwebsite | http://www.ghostmouth.com Full Stack Development

Website for a Minneapolis music project. Utilizes JavaScript, handlebars, HTML, and CSS.

Professional Experience

Minneapolis Public Schools- Reserve Teacher

- Filled in for elementary, middle, and high school teachers at many schools in the Minneapolis Public School district
- Frequently sought after to fill music, technology, and other specialized positions within the district

September 2017-Present

Teachers On Call- Reserve Teacher

Filled in for Paraprofessional Educators at a variety of different schools in the 916
 District, Hopkins, and St. Paul School Systems, with particular focus on schools that specialize in Emotional Behavior Disorders, and Autism

Cause Spirits and Soundbar- Web Developer

- Updated, maintained, and debugged the venue's website
- Implemented a SQL database for the venue's event calendar
- Integrated the website with the venue's various social media pages
- Helped advise the management of the venue on how to increase the establishment's search engine optimization

Spring 2013- July 2014

Banana Static-Web Manager, Public Relations, Content Creator

- Developed, designed, and maintained the website for a Minneapolis Entertainment Web Site that saw some popularity as a music review site
- Maintained email contact and accepted submissions from various publishing companies, record labels, and management teams
- Contributed content to the website

January 2010- June 2012

331- Security

- In charge of managing and training the security staff of the club, ensuring the safety of the staff, and patrons during a variety of different of events that the club hosted
- Helped manage the security team during the Art-A-Whirl event of 2013, 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017, and 2018

Spring 2013- Present

Technical Skills

- Computer Technologies: Javascript, Java, Swift, React.js, jQuery, Node.js, Firebase, MySQL, MongoDB, AJAX, Python, Express, Servers, Database
- Audio Workstations: Experience in Analog Recording and Digital Audio Workstations (Logic Pro, Protools, Harrison Mixbus)
- Visual Editing Suites: Photoshop, ImageGlitch, iMovie, Microsoft Office
- Musical Instruments: Guitar, Piano, Trumpet, Trombone, Flute, Saxophone,
 Synthesizer, Percussion, Double Bass, Clarinet, Harmonica, Mandolin, Banjo, Ukulele

Education

University of Minnesota-Certificate in Web Development

Expected Graduation October 2018

McNally Smith College of Music-Bachelor of Music in Performance

Graduated Spring 2012